here's the graph of the function f
defined by f of x equals 1 over X along
with one label at the input x equals one
now consider another input labeled X
that can vary and draw a line from the
x-axis up to the point on the curve as
we move x to the right we can measure
the area under the curve and above the
x-axis between 1 and the input X the
area is 0 when x equals one and
increases as X increases we can do more
let's actually plot the area on a
separate set of axes like this as X
varies we end up with the curve of a new
function we denote this new function by
capital f of x equals the integral from
1 to X of 1 over T DT and we call this
an area accumulation function of the
function f this particular area
accumulation function is actually one
way to define the natural log notice
that we can let the x value vary less
than one as well resulting in a negative
orientation for the area so this defines
the natural log of x for any X greater
than zero